{
    "exam_metadata": {
        "layout": "exam",
        "title": "Practice Exam 11",
        "exam_id": 11
    },
    "questions": [
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "question_text": "Which options does AWS make available for customers who want to learn about security in the cloud in an instructor-led setting? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Online Tech Talks. | AWS Classroom Training.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Online Tech Talks."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Blog."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Forums."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "AWS Classroom Training."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "question_text": "Which of the following will enhance the security of access to the AWS Management Console\u2019? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Multi-Factor Authentication (AWS MFA). | Password policies.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Secrets Manager."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Certificate Manager."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Multi-Factor Authentication (AWS MFA)."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Security groups."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Password policies."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "question_text": "Which of the following features can be configured through the Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Dashboard? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Security Groups. | Subnets.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront distributions."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Route 53."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Security Groups."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Subnets."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Elastic Load Balancing."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "question_text": "For which auditing process does AWS have sole responsibility?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Physical security.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS IAM policies."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Physical security."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3 bucket policies."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudTrail Logs."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 6,
            "question_text": "Which of the following are advantages of AWS consolidated billing? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "The ability to receive one bill for multiple accounts. | Potential volume discounts, as usage in all accounts is combined.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "The ability to receive one bill for multiple accounts."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Service limits increasing by default in all accounts."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "A fixed discount on the monthly bill."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Potential volume discounts, as usage in all accounts is combined."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "The automatic extension of the master account\u2019s AWS support plan to all accounts."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 7,
            "question_text": "Which of the following common IT tasks can AWS cover to free up company IT resources? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Patching databases software. | Backing up databases.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Patching databases software."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Testing application releases."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Backing up databases."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Creating database schema."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Running penetration tests."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 8,
            "question_text": "A company wants to expand from one AWS Region into a second AWS Region. What does the company need to do to start supporting the new Region?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Begin deploying resources in the second Region.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Contact an AWS Account Manager to sign a new contract."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Move an Availability Zone to the new Region."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Begin deploying resources in the second Region."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Download the AWS Management Console for the new Region."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 9,
            "question_text": "Why is it beneficial to use Elastic Load Balancers with applications?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "They are capable of handling constant changes in network traffic patterns.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "They allow for the conversion from Application Load."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Balancers to Classic Load Balancers."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "They are capable of handling constant changes in network traffic patterns."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "They automatically adjust capacity. They are provided at no charge to users."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 10,
            "question_text": "Which is the MINIMUM AWS Support plan that allows for one-hour target response time for support cases?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Business.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Enterprise."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Business."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Developer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Basic"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 11,
            "question_text": "What is the lowest-cost, durable storage option for retaining database backups for immediate retrieval?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon S3.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Glacier."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EBS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 Instance Store."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 12,
            "question_text": "What AWS team assists customers with accelerating cloud adoption through paid engagements in any of several specialty practice areas?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Professional Services.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Enterprise Support."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Solutions Architects."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Professional Services."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Account Managers."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 13,
            "question_text": "A company needs 24/7 phone email and chat access with a response time of less than 1 hour if a production system has a service interruption Which AWS Support plan meets these requirements at the LOWEST cost?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Business.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Basic."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Developer."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Business."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Enterprise."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 14,
            "question_text": "If a customer needs to audit the change management of AWS resources, which of the following AWS services should the customer use?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Config.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudWatch."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 15,
            "question_text": "How does AWS Trusted Advisor provide guidance to users of the AWS Cloud? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "It provides a list of cost optimization recommendations based on current AWS usage. | It detects potential security vulnerabilities caused by permissions settings on account resources.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "It identifies software vulnerabilities in applications running on AWS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "It provides a list of cost optimization recommendations based on current AWS usage."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "It detects potential security vulnerabilities caused by permissions settings on account resources."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "It automatically corrects potential security issues caused by permissions settings on account resources."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "It provides proactive alerting whenever an Amazon EC2 instance has been compromised."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 16,
            "question_text": "Which AWS managed service is used to host databases?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon RDS.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Batch."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Artifact."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Data Pipeline."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon RDS."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 17,
            "question_text": "Which of the following Identity and Access Management (IAM) entities is associated with an access key ID and secret access key when using AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI)?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "IAM user.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "IAM group."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "IAM user."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "IAM role."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "IAM policy."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 18,
            "question_text": "Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Ensuring that data is encrypted at rest.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring that disk drives are wiped after use."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring that firmware is updated on hardware devices."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring that data is encrypted at rest."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring that network cables are category six or higher."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 19,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides a simple and scalable shared file storage solution for use with Linux-based AWS and on-premises servers?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon EFS.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Glacier."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EBS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EFS."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 20,
            "question_text": "What credential components are required to gain programmatic access to an AWS account? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "An access key ID. | A secret access key.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "An access key ID."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "A primary key."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "A secret access key."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "A user ID."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "A secondary key."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 21,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is a shared control between the customer and AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Awareness.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Providing a key for Amazon S3 client-side encryption."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Configuration of an Amazon EC2 instance."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Environmental controls of physical AWS data centers."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Awareness."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 22,
            "question_text": "Which type of AWS storage is ephemeral and is deleted when an instance is stopped Of terminated?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon EC2 instance store.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EBS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 instance store."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EFS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 23,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an advantage of consolidated billing on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Volume pricing qualification.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Volume pricing qualification."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Shared access permissions."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Multiple bills per account."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Eliminates the need for tagging."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 24,
            "question_text": "Which services are parts of the AWS serverless platform?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Step Functions, Amazon DynamoDB, Amazon SNS.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2, Amazon S3, Amazon Athena."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Kinesis, Amazon SQS, Amazon EMR."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Step Functions, Amazon DynamoDB, Amazon SNS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Athena, Amazon Cognito, Amazon EC2."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 25,
            "question_text": "Which of the following Amazon EC2 pricing models allow customers to use existing server-bound software licenses?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Dedicated Hosts.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Spot Instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Reserved Instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Dedicated Hosts."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "On-Demand Instances."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 26,
            "question_text": "Which of the following security measures protect access to an AWS account? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Grant least privilege access to IAM users. | Activate multi-factor authentication (MFA) for privileged users.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Enable AWS CloudTrail."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Grant least privilege access to IAM users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Create one IAM user and share with many developers and users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Enable Amazon CloudFront."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Activate multi-factor authentication (MFA) for privileged users."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 27,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides the ability to manage infrastructure as code?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS CloudFormation.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodePipeline."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodeDeploy."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudFormation."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 28,
            "question_text": "What is an advantage of deploying an application across multiple Availability Zones?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "The application will have higher availability because it can withstand a service disruption in one Availability Zone.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "There is a lower risk of service failure if a natural disaster causes a service disruption in a given AWS Region."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "The application will have higher availability because it can withstand a service disruption in one Availability Zone."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "There will be better coverage as Availability Zones are geographical^ distant and can serve a wider area."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "There will be decreased application latency that will improve the user experience."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 29,
            "question_text": "A customer needs to run a MySQL database that easily scales. Which AWS service should they use?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Aurora.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Aurora."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Redshift."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon DynamoDB."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon ElastiCache."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 30,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an AWS Cloud architecture design principle?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Implement loose coupling.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Implement single points of failure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Implement loose coupling."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Implement monolithic design."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Implement vertical scaling."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 31,
            "question_text": "AWS Enterprise Support users have access to which service or feature that is not available to users with other AWS Support plans?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Concierge team.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Support case."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Concierge team."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Connect."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 32,
            "question_text": "A company will be moving from an on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud. What would be one financial difference after the move?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Moving from upfront capital expense (capex) to variable operational expense ( opex ).",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Moving from variable operational expense ( opex ) to upfront capital expense (capex)."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Moving from upfront capital expense (capex) to variable capital expense (capex)."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Moving from upfront capital expense (capex) to variable operational expense ( opex )."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Elimination of upfront capital expense (capex) and elimination of variable operational expense ( opex )."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 33,
            "question_text": "When performing a cost analysis that supports physical isolation of a customer workload, which compute hosting model should be accounted for in the Total Cost of Ownership (TCO)?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Dedicated Hosts",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Dedicated Hosts"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Reserved Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "On-Demand Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "No Upfront Reserved Instances"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 34,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service should be used for long-term, low-cost storage of data backups?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Glacier.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon RDS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Glacier."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowball."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS EBS."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 35,
            "question_text": "Which is the MINIMUM AWS Support plan that provides technical support through phone calls?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Business.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Enterprise."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Business."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Developer."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Basic."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 36,
            "question_text": "Which Amazon EC2 instance pricing model can provide discounts of up to 90%?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Spot Instances.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Reserved Instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "On-Demand."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Dedicated Hosts."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Spot Instances."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 37,
            "question_text": "Which of the following AWS services can be used to serve large amounts of online video content with the lowest possible latency? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon S3. | Amazom CloudFront.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "appGateway."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Glacier."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Amazom CloudFront."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 38,
            "question_text": "What can AWS edge locations be used for? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Delivering content closer to users. | Reducing traffic on the server by caching responses.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Hosting applications."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Delivering content closer to users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Running NoSQL database caching services."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Reducing traffic on the server by caching responses."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Sending notification messages to end users."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 39,
            "question_text": "A company is planning to migrate from on-premises to the AWS Cloud. When AWS tool or service provides detailed reports on estimated cost savings after migration?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Cost Explorer."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Migration Hub."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 40,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides a customized view of the health of specific AWS services that power a customer\u2019s workloads running on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Service Health Dashboard."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS X-Ray."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudWatch."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 41,
            "question_text": "One of the advantages to moving infrastructure from an on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud is:",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "It allows the business to focus on business activities.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "It allows the business to eliminate IT bills."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "It allows the business to put a server in each customer\u2019s data center."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "It allows the business to focus on business activities."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "It allows the business to leave servers unpatched."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 42,
            "question_text": "How can an AWS user with an AWS Basic Support plan obtain technical assistance from AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Discussion Forums.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Senior Support Engineers."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Technical Account Managers."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Discussion Forums."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 43,
            "question_text": "How can a user protect against AWS service disruptions if a natural disaster affects an entire geographic area?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Deploy applications across multiple AWS Regions.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Deploy applications across multiple Availability Zones within an AWS Region."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Use a hybrid cloud computing deployment model within the geographic area."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Deploy applications across multiple AWS Regions."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Store application artifacts using AWS Artifact and replicate them across multiple AWS Regions."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 44,
            "question_text": "Which activity is a customer responsibility in the AWS Cloud according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Ensuring Amazon EBS volumes are backed up.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring network connectivity from AWS to the internet."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Patching and fixing flaws within the AWS Cloud infrastructure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring the physical security of cloud data centers."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring Amazon EBS volumes are backed up."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 45,
            "question_text": "In which scenario should Amazon EC2 Spot Instances be used?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "A company has a number of infrequent, interruptible jobs that are currently using On-Demand Instances.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "A company wants to move its main website to AWS from an on-premises web server."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "A company has a number of application services whose Service Level Agreement (SLA) requires 99.999% uptime."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "A company\u2019s heavily used legacy database is currently running on-premises."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "A company has a number of infrequent, interruptible jobs that are currently using On-Demand Instances."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 46,
            "question_text": "A customer is deploying a new application and needs to choose an AWS Region. Which of the following factors could influence the customer\u2019s decision? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Reduced latency to users. | Data sovereignty compliance.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Reduced latency to users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "The application\u2019s presentation in the local language."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Data sovereignty compliance."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Cooling costs in hotter climates."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Proximity to the customer\u2019s office for on-site visits."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 47,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides alerts when an AWS event may impact a company\u2019s AWS resources?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Service Health Dashboard."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Infrastructure Event Management."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 48,
            "question_text": "Which disaster recovery scenario offers the lowest probability of down time?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Multi-site active-active.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Backup and restore."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Pilot light."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Warm standby."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Multi-site active-active."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 49,
            "question_text": "Which service\u2019s PRIMARY purpose is software version control?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS CodeCommit.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CodeStar."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI)."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Cognito."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodeCommit."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 50,
            "question_text": "How can a customer increase security to AWS account logons? (Select TWO)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Enable Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) | Configure a strong password policy",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Configure AWS Certificate Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Enable Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Use Amazon Cognito to manage access"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Configure a strong password policy"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Enable AWS Organizations"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}